skinnydiplondon.com 2019-12-18

# Privacy Policy | Skinnydip London

**It’s the words on everyone’s lips – Data Protection.**

**Don’t worry we have you covered & we only do what is right for you.**

**Privacy**

Skinnydip Ltd is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected.  As always, our customers are our top priority. This privacy policy sets out how Skinnydip Ltd uses and protects any information that you give us when you use this website. Skinnydip Ltd may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. We want to inform you of all your rights relating to your information. 

**What information do we collect?**

_Things we collect include:_

  * Name
  * Contact Details
  * Date of Birth
  * Gender Information
  * Payment Information
  * When you contact us
  * IP Address
  * Purchase History
  * Wishlist
  * Device Type
  * Operating System
  * Location Data
  * Your response to promotions

We may also obtain data surrounding how you use the website to help us develop and improve the site.

**What do we do with the information we gather?**

That might seem like a lot but the reason behind our data collection is to ensure that we give you the best service we possibly can.  This information allows us to get your order out to you, let you know when it is coming and prevent fraud. 

We also use the above data to give you what you want, let you see our fab new products and if there are any hot promotions on at the moment.  We only want to provide the best user experience for our customers.

We may occasionally send out emails concerning new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided. You can stop these at any time by:

  * Contacting us directly by calling our Customer Service team on 02087952706 or emailing us on [mail@skinnydiplondon.com](mailto:mail@skinnydiplondon.com)
  * By clicking ‘unsubscribe’ in any of the marketing messages you receive, this can typically be found at the bottom of email

Please allow up to 3 days for this to take effect.

**Remarketing**

One of the tools we use to keep you as up to date as possible with the low down at Skinnydip is targeted adverts.

You will see these adverts across other websites and apps outside of the Skinnydip realm.  They will include products and services that we think you will be interested in, based on what you have viewed or bought on our website.  We obtain this information via web beacons, pixels, tags, cookies or by services that are offered by websites and social media networks.

**How do you get my consent?**  
When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, verify your credit card, place an order, arrange for a delivery or return a purchase, we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only.

If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent, or provide you with an opportunity to say no.

If after you opt-in, you change your mind, you can withdraw your consent for us to contact you - for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information; or to fully delete you from our records at anytime, by contacting us at [mail@skinnydiplondon.com](mailto:mail@skinnydiplondon.com)

We got your back.

**Shopify**  
We host our store on Shopify Inc. They provide us with the online e-commerce platform that allows us to sell our products and services to you. All your data is stored through Shopify's data storage, databases and the general Shopify application. All data is stored behind a firewall on a secure server. 

**Payment:**

If you choose a direct payment gateway to complete your purchase, then Shopify stores your credit card data. It is encrypted through the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI-DSS). Your purchase transaction data is stored only as long as is necessary to complete your purchase transaction. After that is complete, your purchase transaction information is deleted.

All direct payment gateways adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, Mastercard, American Express and Discover.

PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of credit card information by our store and its service providers.

For more insight, you may also want to read Shopify’s Terms of Service (<https://www.shopify.com/legal/terms>) or Privacy Statement (<https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy)>.

**Third Party Services**

Skinnydip will not disclose any of your information to any third parties except in a situation where it is part of providing a service to you. This includes arranging for a product to be sent to you, carrying out security checks and for the purposes of customer research or when you have given us permission to do so. 

In general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us.

However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions.

For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies, so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these providers.

One of the Third Party payment services we use is Klarna.  We work with Klarna to offer our customers more convenient methods of payment. Klarna's principal place of business is at Sveavägen 46, 111 34 Stockholm, Sweden. Klarna is registered with the Swedish companies register under the registration number 556737-0431 and licensed by and under the supervision of the Swedish Financial Supervisory Authority (www.fi.se), Box 7821, 10397 Stockholm, Sweden, and the Swedish Data Protection Authority ([http://www.datainspektionen.se/in-english/](https://www.datainspektionen.se/in-english/ "The Swedish Data Protection Authority")), Box 8114, 10420 Stockholm, Sweden.  To read their full privacy policy, please visit their website here: <http://cdn.klarna.com/1.0/shared/content/legal/terms/Klarna/en_gb/privacy>

Please do remember that certain providers may be in or have facilities that are located a different jurisdiction than either you or us. So if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service provider, then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located.

As an example, if you are in Canada and your transaction is processed by a payment gateway located in the United States, then your personal information used in completing that transaction may be subject to disclosure under United States legislation, including the Patriot Act.

Once you leave our store’s website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website’s Terms of Service. Please see below for a list of Third Party Services we use and a direct link to their privacy policy page.

Paypal - <https://www.paypal.com/en/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full>

Klayivo - <https://www.klaviyo.com/privacy>

Zendesk - <https://www.zendesk.co.uk/company/customers-partners/privacy-policy/>

Amazon Payments - <https://pay.amazon.com/uk/help/201751600>

Unidays - <https://www.myunidays.com/GB/en-GB/privacy-policy>

Student Beans - <https://www.studentbeans.com/uk/info/privacy>

Wufoo - <https://www.wufoo.com/privacy/2016-01-18/>

AWin - <https://www.awin.com/gb/legal/privacy-policy>

Hotjar - <https://www.hotjar.com/privacy>

Mail Chimp - <https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/>

Google Analytics - <https://policies.google.com/privacy>

Facebook - <https://www.facebook.com/full_data_use_policy>

Youtube - <https://support.google.com/youtube/answer/7671399?hl=en>

Treatwell - <https://www.treatwell.co.uk/info/privacy-policy/>

Instagram - <https://help.instagram.com/155833707900388>

Pinterest - <https://help.instagram.com/155833707900388>

Twitter - <https://twitter.com/en/privacy>

Salonized - <https://www.salonized.com/en/privacy-statement>

Yotpo - <https://www.yotpo.com/privacy-policy/>

Loyalty Lion - <https://loyaltylion.com/privacy>

Doddle - <https://doodle.com/privacy-policy>

Torque - <https://www.torque.eu/privacy-and-cookies-policy/>

Hermes – <https://www.myhermes.co.uk/privacy-policy.html>

OCS – <https://www.ocsworldwide.co.uk/GDPR/OCS_Privacy_Notice.pdf>

Okendo - <https://www.okendo.io/privacy-policy/>

Nosto - <https://www.nosto.com/terms/dpa/>

HubBox - <https://www.hub-box.com/privacy-policy/>

**Social Media**

Skinnydip was built on social media.  We love to see what our Skinnydip customers are wearing and keep in contact with you guys! We recognise that social media offers a platform for our company to perform marketing, stay connected with customers and build our profile online.

If you interact with us on social media, you are consenting and allowing us to interact with you.  An interaction can be defined as liking or following our SM accounts, commenting or tagging us in photos or post and sharing our content via liking or retweeting.  From this interaction, we may collect data that will help enhance your experience with us in the future.

If you tag us in a photograph that we rate, you may be lucky enough for us to share it across our SM accounts - organic or paid.  By interacting with us, you are consenting that we can use images or comments royalty free without limitation.  If you are unhappy with us sharing your comments or images, please do let us know and we will stop.

**Security**  
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure.  We take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not appropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.

To prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. If you provide us with your credit card information, the information is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL) and stored with AES-256 encryption. Although no method of transmission over the internet or electronic stores is 100% secure, we follow all PCI-DSS requirements and implement additional generally accepted industry standards. We may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so or if you violate our Terms of Service.

We hold all your information until you no longer hold an account with us or until you specify that you no longer want us to hear from us.

**Cookies**  
Sadly, not the cookies that we love to eat! A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual and help us to provide you with a better website, tailoring it to your needs. You can choose to accept or decline cookies, this may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website. 

The four main types of cookies we use are:

  * Site functionality Cookie
  * Website Analytic Cookie
  * Personalisation Cookie
  * Segmentation and Targeting Cookie.

**Age of Consent**

By using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.

We do not knowingly collect the data of anyone under the age of consent on our website.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.

If our store is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to sell products to you.

**Questions and Contact Information**

If you would like to:

  * access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you,
  * register a complain
  * simply want more information,

contact our Privacy Compliance Officer at: mail@skinnydiplondon.com or by mail at

FAO Privacy Compliance Officer

Skinnydip London

1 Whittlebury Mews West,

London,

NW1 8JB

Updated: 14/5/2018
